Guide to the Rice University Dean of Undergraduates records, 1965-2004 UA 144
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Dean of Undergraduates records
1950-2009
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University. Office of the Dean of Undergraduates
UA 144
16 Linear Feet (28 boxes and 2 cartons)
Records reflecting the daily business of the Rice University Dean of Undergraduates, 1950-2009.
Biographical / Historical
The Dean of Undergraduates at Rice University is responsible for overseeing and bringing together the many components of undergraduate life. This is achieved by addressing both the academic as well as the noncurricular aspects of student life through a variety of programs and resources, with the ultimate aim of creating a comprehensive undergraduate experience. Areas of responsibility include academic advising, career services, judicial affairs, student affairs, student health, student recreation, undergraduate research and fellowships, and international programs.
Scope and Contents
Records reflecting the daily business of the Rice University Dean of Undergraduates, 1965-2004. Main groupings include college courses, university council, committees, surveys, college information including budgets.
Restrictions on Access
This material is open for research with the exception of Series V: Board of Trustees meeting minutes, which requires written permission from Board for access. Ask Woodson staff for assistance in requesting permission.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Note
This material was transfered to the Woodson Research Center in 2008 and 2011.
Index Terms
Subjects
Social life and customs; Universities and colleges
Document Types
notes; reports; minutes (administrative records)
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University; Rice University. Office of the Dean of Undergraduates
- Series I: College Courses, 1970-1989
  - College Courses Fall 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - College Courses 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - College Courses Fall 1977-Spring 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - College Courses Fall 1979-Spring 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - College Courses Fall 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - College Courses Fall 1980-Spring 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - College Courses Fall 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - College Courses Fall 1982-Spring 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - College Courses Fall 1983-Spring 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - College Courses Fall 1984-Spring 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - College Courses Fall 1985-Spring 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - College Courses Fall 1986-Spring 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - College Courses Fall 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - College Courses Fall 1988-Spring 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Series II: University council and related committees, 1971-1998
  - University Council 1989-90 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - University Council 1990-91 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - University Council 1991-92 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - University Council 1992-93 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - University Council 1993-94 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - University Council 1994-95 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Operations Council 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Operations Council 1996-97 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Operations Council 1997-98 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Operations Council 1998-99 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University Council 1989-90 Promotion/Tenure (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - University Council/Promotion and Tenure 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - University Council-Promotion and Tenure 1991-92 Advocates (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Promotion and Tenure Committee 1992-93 Advocates (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meetings 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting 1991-92/Calendar Consideration 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meetings 1992-93 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meetings 1993-94 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meetings 1994-95 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meetings 1995-96 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meetings 1996-97 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1997-98 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting 1998-99 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - For President's Report 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Series III: Committees and Surveys, 1973-2003
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing 1975-76 KTB-ex off (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing 1976-77 KTB, ex off (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1979-80 KB, ex off (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Examinations and Standing Comm 1973-74 KTB-Ex officio (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Examinations and Standing Comm 1974-75 KTB-ex officio (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1980-81 KB, ex off (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1981-82 KB/ex off (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1982-83 KB, ex off (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1983-84 RFS-Ex officio (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1984-85 RFS, ex officio (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1985-86 RFS, ex off (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1986-87 RFS, Advisor (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1987-88 RFS, Advisor (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1988-89 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1992-93 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1993-94 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Examinations And Standing 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gradation: Courses Taken Outside Rice University (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing Minutes 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing Correspondence 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Examination and Standing (EX and S) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing Minutes 1996-97 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing Minutes 1996-97 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing 1996-97 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing 1997-98 Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing Original Minutes 1997-98 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing 1997-98 List and Labels (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Examinations and Standing 1997-98 Minutes (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Coed Colleges 1970-71 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Residential Colleges (Buildings and Grounds) 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Implementation of Coed Colleges 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Coed College Recommendation 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Brown-Sid Conversion 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Masters and Colleges General 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - College Occupancy Miscellaneous Information 1974-75 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Some History Concerning College Masters (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Changes in College Rules-Masters (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - College Course Review Committee (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ford Foundation Honors Program (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Committees (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Masters Compensation (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - College Masters Committee 1975-76 KTB, ex off (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - College Masters Committee 1976-77 KTB, ex off (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the College Masters 1977-78 KTB, ex off (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Committee of the College Masters KB, ex officio 1978-79 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Committee of the College Masters 1979-80 KB, ex off (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - College Masters 1980-81 KB, ex off (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Committee of the College Masters 81-82 KB/ex off (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Committee of College Masters 1982-83 KB, ex officio (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Committee of the College Masters 1983-84 RFS-ex officio (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - College Masters 1984-85 RFS-ex off (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Committee of the College Masters 1985-86 RFS, ex off (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Committee of the College Masters 1986-87 RFS, Advisor (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Committee of the College Masters 1987-88 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - College Masters 1988-89 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - College Masters 1989-90 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - College Masters 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - College Masters 1991-92 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Committee of the Masters 1993-94 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - College Masters 1994-95 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Masters' Meetings 1995-96 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Masters' Meetings 1996-97 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - College Masters 1996-97 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Masters 1997-98 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - College Masters 1998-99 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Princeton Review 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Wintergreen/Orchard House Survey 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Misc Surveys 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Surveys 2001-2002 did not participate (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - US News 2002 (Spring 2002) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Common Data Set 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Misc. 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Inst. Research Rome, GA (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Misc Surveys 2003 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - College Profiles 2003 (Trinity Software) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - College Scope Survey 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Fulbright Int'l Survey 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - College Bound 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - ECIS-European Council of Int'l Schools Spring 2003 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hispanic Program Survey for Univ. of South Florida 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Octameron Assoc-Scholarship Survey 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - US News (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Misc (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Surveys '00 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - US News and World Rpt Spring 2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Career Services Survey (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - College Board Survey 2001-2002 (Spring 2001) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ACT Institutional DataQues. Response Spring 2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Misc Surveys 2000-2001 Responses (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Survey Info-Misc (2001) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Princeton Review-Survey 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Peterson's Campus Visit Survey (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Peterson's Int'l Student Survey Spring 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kaplan/Newsweek Survey 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Cambridge Assoc. Survey Fall 2000 and Fall 2001 Completed by SFS (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Misc Surveys-Rice not participating 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Newsweek/Kaplan's Guide: How to get into College 01-02 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Barron's Best Buys in College Edu. 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Blacks in Higher Ed.-Survey Fall 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - European Council of Int'l Schools 2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hispanic Journal-Survey 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ACT Institutional DataQuest 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - The College Board-Annual Survey 2002-2003 Survey in year 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Factual Sketch 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Class of 2006 Summary (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - TEN (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hobsons (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - ALC (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - T.E.S. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - NACAC (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Inst. Research (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Worth (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Princeton Review 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - ACT 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kaplan (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Fiske Guide to Colleges "2005" (2002-2003 info) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Institutional Research for Admission link to Stats for Prosp. Stud (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - I.S.I. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publications 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Com. 1973-74 KTB-member (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Committee 1974-75 KTB-member (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1975-76 KTB, member (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1976-77 KTB, ex off (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Committee on undergraduate Teaching 1977-78 KTB, ex off (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1978-79 KB, ex officio (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1979-1980 KB, ex off (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1980-81 KB, ex off (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Teaching 81-82 KB/ex off (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 82-83 KB, ex off (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1983-84 RFS-ex officio (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1984-85 RFS-ex off (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1985-86 RFS ex off (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1986-87 RFS, Advisor (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1987-88 RFS, Advisor (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1988-89 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Teaching 1994-95 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Committee Undergraduate Starts Fall 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Com 1973-74 KTB-ex-officio (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Comm. 1974-75 KTB-ex officio (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1975-76 KTB, ex off (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1976-77 KTB, ex off (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1977-78 KTB, ex off (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum KB, ex officio 1978-79 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1979-80 KB, ex off (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1980-81 KB, ex off (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 81-82 KB, ex off (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 82-83 KB, ex off (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1983-84 RFS-ex officio (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1984-85 RFS-ex off (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1985-86 RFS ex off (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1986-87 RFS, Advis. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum1987-88 RFS, advisor (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1988-89 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1989-90 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1991-92 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1992-93 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1993-94 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1994-95 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1995-96 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum 1997-98 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Undergraduate Curriculum 1998-99 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Series IV: College Information, 1965-2004
  - Baker College (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Baker College 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Baker College 1972-1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Brown College 1968-1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Brown College 1965-66, 1966-67 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Brown College 1972-1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hanszen College 1972-1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hanszen College 1967- (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Jones College 1972-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Jones College 1965- (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lovett College 1972-1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lovett College 1968- (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Richardson College Night (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Richardson College 1972-1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Richardson College 1970- (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Wiess College (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Wiess College 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Wiess College 1972-1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Will Rice College 1965-66, 1966-67 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Will Rice College 1967-68 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Will Rice College 1968-69 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Will Rice College 1969-70 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Will Rice College 1970-71 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Will Rice College 1972-1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - College Masters Budget FY 03 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Baker College Budget FY 03 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Brown College Budget FY 03 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hanszen College Budget FY 03 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Hanszen College Budget FY 03 Part II (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jones College Budget FY 03 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Jones College Budget FY 03 Part II (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lovett College Budget FY 03 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Martel College Budget FY 03 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Richardson College Budget FY 03 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Wiess College Budget FY 03 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Wiess College Budget FY 03 Part II (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Will Rice College Budget FY 03 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Will Rice College Budget FY 03 Part II (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - College Masters Budget 04 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Baker College Budget FY 04 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Brown College Budget FY 04 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Brown College Budget FY 04 Part II (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Hanszen College Budget FY 04 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Hanszen College Budget FY 04 Part II (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Jones College Budget FY 04 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Jones College Budget FY 04 Part II (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lovett College Budget FY 04 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Martel College Budget FY 04 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Richardson College Budget FY 04 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Wiess College Budget FY 04 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Wiess College Budget FY 04 Part II (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Will Rice College Budget FY 04 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Will Rice College Budget FY 04 Part II (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Series V: Board of Trustees meeting notes, 2001-2004
  General note
  This material is restricted and requires written permission from Board of Trustees for access. Ask Woodson staff for assistance in requesting permission.
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Dec. 11-12, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. Dec. 11-12, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. March 13-14, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. May 22-23, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - New Trustees Orientation 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. September 18-19, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. December 10-11, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - New Trustees Orientation Zenaido Camacho (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. March 26-27, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Mtg. May 14-15, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting October 1-2, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting December 16-17, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting March 24-25, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting May 12-13, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Addendum: Histories and Policies, 1964-1992
  - History of the Office of Undergraduate Affairs, 1964-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Policy File:Responsibilities and Duties in Student Affairs, 1965-1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Policy File - Off-Campus Women, 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Final Copy - Cullen Scholars Program, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Duke University - Minority Recruitment, 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Minority Student Recruitment, 1990, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Recruitment Update, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Academic Advisor to Student Athletes May - Dec., 1983 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Rice Memorial Center Expansion Proposal by Rice University Student Association, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Campaign and Preliminary Plans for New Student Center, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Campaign for New Student Center, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Ley Student Center Dedication Space, Furnishings, Usage, Alumni Fundraising, 1986-1991 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Matt Taylor, Associate Dean of Undergraduates 1950-2009
  - Committee on the Rice Undergraduate Program (CRUP) Original Notes/Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Wiess Plan and Perspective, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Committee on the Rice Undergraduate Program (CRUP) Report Drafts, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Quality Enhancement Plan (QEP) and Committee on the Rice Undergraduate Program (CRUP) Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Committee on the Rice Undergraduate Program (CRUP) E-Mails, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Rice Undergraduate Program (CRUP) Resources, 2005-2007 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Notes and E-Mails, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: McMurtry Groundbreaking, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Ambassador Training, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Ambassadors, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Transfer Data, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Transfer Plan, 2009-2010 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Housing Plans, 2009-2010 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - McMurtry/Duncan: Populating the New Colleges, 2008-2009 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Social Norms Info, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Parking, 2010-2011 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Parking, 2007-2010 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Masters/RAs Housing Agreement, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Constitution Day, 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - College Teams/Training, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE) Report on Staffing, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Tulane/Hurricane, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Thresher, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - "Size" Task Force, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Martel Formation, 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Volunteers in Service to America (VISTA), 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) On-Site Evaluation, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP) Site Visit, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Student Advising Group, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Supplemental Objectives- Student and Staff Input, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Peer Institutions' Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - National Survey of Student Engagement (NSSE) Registration, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP) Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Meetings and E-Mail, 2004-2006 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Advisory Board, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP) Letters/DRAFTS, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Lit Review for Quality Enhancement Program (QEP), 2005 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Courses/Principle Design, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): "The Center", 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Community Partners Quality Enhancement Program (QEP), 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Consultants, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Campus Compact, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Boniuk Center/Ford Grant, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP) Rationale/Bibliography, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Budget, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Boyer Report, 2000-2003 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Atlanta/Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), 2005 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Center for Civic Engagement, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 48)